Lowell Thomas
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Lowell Thomas, 2.1.3.3.3
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, circa late 1800s; 5 (Box 1523)
    - Note: Additional Fredstone - Cripple Creek pix. (Did you want to send one to the Cripple Creek paper?), 1
    - Caption: Leo Ruschenberg's Cabin; Cripple Creek /93/ Fred Stone/ Bert Ragan / Youngdale[?]/ Leo Welch, 2
    - Verso: Dear Lowell Thomas, This is a picture of our cabin in Cripple Creek. You once told me you were born there in 1893. This cabin is back of our theatre. I am on the extreme left of the picture. Each of the others were musicians and each had a job to do. They called me "Jimmy Gets" ( get-the- wood- and- water- boy ). Also actor - I hoped! Merry Christmas to you. [signed] Fred Stone, 2-verso
    - Caption: Leo Ruschenberg's Cabin; Cripple Creek /93/ Fred Stone/ Bert Ragan / Youngdale[?]/ Leo Welch, 3
    - Caption: Leo Ruschenberg's Cabin; Cripple Creek /93/ Fred Stone/ Bert Ragan / Youngdale[?]/ Leo Welch, 4
    - Caption: Leo Ruschenberg's Cabin; Cripple Creek /93/ Fred Stone/ Bert Ragan / Youngdale[?]/ Leo Welch, 5
    - [view with hills and train tracks], 6
    - Cripple Creek, 7
    - Cripple Creek, 8
    - Verso: Cripple Creek, 8-verso
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, circa 1900 - 1912; 6 (Box 1523)
    - Garfield School, Victor, Colo. [Lowell Thomas seated third from right], 1
    - [grade school class photograph. Lowell Thomas second from right in middle row of standing children], 2
    - L.T. seated on left. Cripple Track Team. L.T. age 13, 3
    - Verso: L.T. seated on left. Cripple Track Team. L.T. age 13, 3-verso
    - Note: Victor High School track team 1907 or 1908 Standing, left to right: 1. Coach Boughton 2. ?? 3. Leslie Schoen 4. Joe Brill 5. Walter Schoen 6. Homer Huffaker Seated: 1. Lowell Thomas 2. Harry Black 3. Donald Kennedy 4. ?Vincent? Reclining: Clyde Black The Lowell Thomas Museum, Victor Colorado Dear Friends: Among some old pictures I found this one of the Victor High School track team, taken in 1907 or 1908, and I thought you might like to have it for your collection. Sincerely yours, Homer Huffaker Chino Valley, Arizona November 27, 1963, 4
    - Cripple Creek track team, L.T. seated on left, 5
    - Cripple Creek track team, L.T. seated on left, 6
    - LT in 1906 - age 14 riding for the Portland Mine. Getting gold samples from other mines to be assayed., 7
    - LT in 1906 - age 14 riding for the Portland Mine. Getting gold samples from other mines to be assayed., 8
    - Verso: LT in 1906 - age 14 riding for the Portland Mine. Getting gold samples from other mines to be assayed., 8-verso
    - Note: LT in 1906 - age 14 riding for the Portland Mine. Getting gold samples from other mines to be assayed., 9
    - Victor High School [football] team, 1908; Verso: Front row, left to right: Donald Kennedy, [Marian?][Monty?] Grice, Joe Brill; Second row, left to right: Andy George, Bill or Will Hayes, Lowell Thomas, Harry Black; Third row, left to right: Leonard Hart, Rene [Guerin?][Guarin?], Orin [Devy?], manager, Chas. Eby, "Midge" Fryberger; Back row: [Professor] Geo. Craig, coach, Ray Shaw, 10
    - Verso: Front row, left to right: Donald Kennedy, [Marian?][Monty?] Grice, Joe Brill; Second row, left to right: Andy George, Bill or Will Hayes, Lowell Thomas, Harry Black; Third row, left to right: Leonard Hart, Rene [Guerin?][Guarin?], Orin [Devy?], manager, Chas. Eby, "Midge" Fryberger; Back row: [Professor] Geo. Craig, coach, Ray Shaw, 10-verso
    - Note: Victor High School [football] team, 1908; Verso: Front row, left to right: Donald Kennedy, [Marian?][Monty?] Grice, Joe Brill; Second row, left to right: Andy George, Bill or Will Hayes, Lowell Thomas, Harry Black; Third row, left to right: Leonard Hart, Rene [Guerin?][Guarin?], Orin [Devy?], manager, Chas. Eby, "Midge" Fryberger; Back row: [Professor] Geo. Craig, coach, Ray Shaw, 11
    - Note: Victor High School [football] team, 1908; Verso: Front row, left to right: Donald Kennedy, [Marian?][Monty?] Grice, Joe Brill; Second row, left to right: Andy George, Bill or Will Hayes, Lowell Thomas, Harry Black; Third row, left to right: Leonard Hart, Rene [Guerin?][Guarin?], Orin [Devy?], manager, Chas. Eby, "Midge" Fryberger; Back row: [Professor] Geo. Craig, coach, Ray Shaw, 12
    - Victor High School football team, 1908, L.t. second row, second from right, 13
    - Victor High School football team, 1908, L.t. second row, second from right, 14
    - Victor High School football team, 1908, L.t. second row, second from right, 15
    - Lowell Thomas sitting in the snow (Thomas the eighteen-year old miner, in the Colorado mountains near Cripple Creek), 16
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas sitting in the snow, 16-verso
    - Lowell Thomas sitting in the snow (Thomas the eighteen-year old miner, in the Colorado mountains near Cripple Creek), 17
    - Note: Thomas the eighteen-year old miner, in the Colorado mountains near Cripple Creek, 18
    - L.T. as an 18 year old minor (first job after college), 19
    - Note: 1st job after college; 1911 - job - pick and shovel, 20
    - Note: L.T. in his mining days. Age - 18, 21
    - L.T. as an 18 year old minor (first job after college), 22
    - Note: Letter to Frances Ryan, 23
    - L.T. as an 18 year old minor (first job after college), 24
    - Verso: L.T. the young miner; Victor, Colorado - about 1909, 24-verso
    - L.T.: About 1911 as near as I can judge, 25
    - Verso: About 1911 as near as I can judge, 25-verso
    - Note: Lowell Thomas when editor of the daily paper in Colorado in 1911-1912, 26
    - L.T.: About 1911 as near as I can judge, 27
    - L.T.: About 1911 as near as I can judge, 28
    - Professor Taylor, Principle of Victor High School, 29
    - Note: Professor Taylor, Principal of the Victor High School, friend of my father, and a top flight educator. He's one of two of my teachers who actually gave me a licking. The other was a woman, an amazon who was my teacher in the 8th grade. She also was a great person and I'm sorry I've forgotten her name. I believe she later became a doctor in Fort Collins, Colorado. Professor Taylor was quite right in giving me that licking?, 30
    - Caption: Victor, Colorado - "The City of Mines" (early 1900s); Photo by Hileman - 1911, 31
    - Caption: Victor, Colo[rado], City of Mines, 32
    - Verso: [illegible] Victor Museum, 32-verso
    - Note: Looking west over the city of Victor, Colorado, around 1900, 33
    - [Lowell Thomas, left(?) with group of men in swimming outfits, one in suit], 34
    - [man on top of traincar(?)], 35
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado [Lowell Thomas and Governor Ralph Carr visit], 1939; 7 (Box 1523)
    - [group of men(?)], July 24 1939, 1
    - [Lowell Thomas(?) 3rd from left, with group of people outside of a house], July 24 1939, 2
    - [Lowell Thomas(?) in hat with two men and a women outside of a building], July 24 1939, 3
    - [Lowell Thomas(?) on right with group of men outside a newspaper office(?)], July 24 1939, 4
    - [Lowell Thomas on right with two other men], July 24 1939, 5
    - [Lowell Thomas in car with another man], July 24 1939, 6
    - [Lowell Thomas with donkey and woman], July 24 1939, 7
    - [View of town, Victor, Colorado (?)], July 24 1939, 8
    - [Lowell Thomas(?) standing on the steps of a house], July 24 1939, 9
    - [Lowell Thomas(?) standing in front of a house], July 24 1939, 10
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado [Lowell Thomas and Governor Ralph Carr visit], circa 1940s; 8 (Box 1523)
    - Lowell Thomas, center, points out object to his son, left, while former Governor of Colorado, Ralph Carr, looks on. The three are standing in front of the old Victor Record Bldg. Thomas, son of the Miller's family physician, is a former Record newsboy. Carr served as a reporter on the Record before completing his law studies., 1
    - Note: Lowell Thomas, center, points out object to his son, left, while former Governor of Colorado, Ralph Carr, looks on. The three are standing in front of the old Victor Record Bldg. Thomas, son of the Miller's family physician, is a former Record newsboy. Carr served as a reporter on the Record before completing his law studies., 2
    - [Three men], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas, back center, with a group of people], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas, back center, with a group of people], 5
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado [dedication of the Lowell Thomas ski jump, Tenderfoot Hill] [ groundbreaking at new mill], 1949; 9 (Box 1523)
    - Taken by Art Hansen - miner; A. W. Oliver - Ben Hill - Dr. De[?]; Lowell Jr. (back); Rorabaugh Mayor of Cr[?], 1
    - Verso: Taken by Art Hansen - miner; A. W. Oliver - Ben Hill - Dr. De[?]; Lowell Jr. (back); Rorabaugh Mayor of Cr[?], 1-verso
    - For Lowell Jr., 2
    - Verso: For Lowell Jr., 2-verso
    - Gr. Br. New mill - [?] - late 1940s, 3
    - Verso: Gr. Br. New mill - [?] - late 1940s, 3-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, breaking ground for new mill(?)], 4
    - Dedic[ation] of L.T. ski jump - Tenderfoot Hill, Cripple Creek - Jan. 27, 1949, 5
    - Verso: Dedic[ation] of L.T. ski jump - Tenderfoot Hill, Cripple Creek - Jan. 27, 1949, 5-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, left, with group of men on stage], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) in crowd at train station ], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas in crowd at train station], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group fo people posing on a train], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) with group on platform], 10
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado [Carlton Mill opening], 1951; 10 (Box 1523)
    - A donkey used by Elza Fay (left) in his role as a gold prospector provided a picturesque prop Monday for photographers snapping pictures after the parade in Cripple Creek which raised the curtain on activities in connection with the Carlton Mill. Mrs. A. E. Carlton, widow of one of the men after whom the mill is named, is also shown in the picture with Lowell Thomas, who dedicated the mill, 1
    - Note: [newspaper clipping] A donkey used by Elza Fay (left) in his role as a gold prospector provided a picturesque prop Monday for photographers snapping pictures after the parade in Cripple Creek which raised the curtain on activities in connection with the Carlton mill. Mrs. A. E. Carlton, widow of one of the men after whom the mill is named, is also shown in the picture with Lowell Thomas, who dedicated the mill, 2
    - Carlton Mill dedication in March, 1951, 3
    - Carlton Mill dedication in March, 1951, 4
    - Carlton Mill dedication in March, 1951, 5
    - Carlton Mill dedication in March, 1951, 6
    - Carlton Mill dedication in March, 1951, 7
    - Carlton Mill dedication in March, 1951, 8
    - Carlton Mill dedication in March, 1951, 9
    - Carlton Mill dedication in March, 1951, 10
    - Carlton Mill dedication in March, 1951, 11
    - Carlton Mill dedication in March, 1951, 12
    - Carlton Mill dedication in March, 1951, 13
    - Carlton Mill dedication in March, 1951, 14
    - Carlton Mill dedication in March, 1951, 15
    - Note: Carlton Mill dedication in March, 1951, 16
    - Note: Cripple Creek Duplicates, From Max W. Bowen, The Golden cycle CPN P.O. Box 86, Colorado Springs, Colorado. To Mr. Lowell Thomas, Hammersley Hill, Pawling, NY, 17
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado [Carlton Mill opening], 1951; 11 (Box 1523)
    - There was lots to talk about when two "old-timers" of the Cripple Creek-Victor district, John White, left, and Dr. H. G. Thomas, right, got together Monday in Cripple Creek. Listening to the reminiscing by the pair at Cripple Creek Elks club building is Mrs. Pherbia Thornburg, daughter of Dr. Thomas and sister of Radio News Commentator Lowell Thomas, 1
    - Note: There was lots to talk about when two "old-timers" of the Cripple Creek-Victor district, John White, left, and Dr. H. G. Thomas, right, got together Monday in Cripple Creek. Listening to the reminiscing by the pair at Cripple Creek Elks club building is Mrs. Pherbia Thornburg, daughter of Dr. Thomas and sister of Radio News Commentator Lowell Thomas, 2
    - Shown addressing the nearly 3,000 persons who attended dedication ceremonies of the Carlton mill Monday in Cripple Creek-Victor gold district is Merrill E. Shoup, president of the Golden Cycle corporation, builder of the mill and owner of mines in the district. In the front row immediately behind Shoup are, left to right, Mrs. Ethel Carlton, a director of the corporation and widow of A. E. Carlton, mining man; Lowell Thomas, CBS news commentator; Max Bowen, Golden Cycle vice-president; Mrs. A. C. Magruder, sister of the late A. E. and L. G. Carlton, and Dr. H. G. Thomas, early day Victor physician and father of Lowell Thomas, 3
    - Note: Shown addressing the nearly 3,000 persons who attended dedication ceremonies of the Carlton mill Monday in Cripple Creek-Victor gold district is Merrill E. Shoup, president of the Golden Cycle corporation, builder of the mill and owner of mines in the district. In the front row immediately behind Shoup are, left to right, Mrs. Ethel Carlton, a director of the corporation and widow of A. E. Carlton, mining man; Lowell Thomas, CBS news commentator; Max Bowen, Golden Cycle vice-president; Mrs. A. C. Magruder, sister of the late A. E. and L. G. Carlton, and Dr. H. G. Thomas, early day Victor physician and father of Lowell Thomas, 4
    - Lowell Thomas, the district's favorite son, on Monday, March [?], pushed a very important button. The button started the wheels turning in the huge Carlton gold reduction mill just completed by the Golden Cycle corporation, 5
    - Note: Lowell Thomas, the district's favorite son, on Monday, March [?], pushed a very important button. The button started the wheels turning in the huge Carlton gold reduction mill just completed by the Golden Cycle corporation, 6
    - Carlton Mill opening in March, 1951, 7
    - Carlton Mill opening in March, 1951, 8
    - Carlton Mill opening in March, 1951, 9
    - Carlton Mill opening in March, 1951, 10
    - Carlton Mill opening in March, 1951, 11
    - Carlton Mill opening in March, 1951, 12
    - Carlton Mill opening in March, 1951, 13
    - Carlton Mill opening in March, 1951, 14
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, circa 1950s; 12 (Box 1523)
    - [Lowell Thomas, center, with man and woman], 1
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado [color photographs], circa 1960s; 13 (Box 1523)
    - [Lowell Thomas with man and woman pointing to a plaque of directors V.C. Hills (?)], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with police officer in front of the plaque of directors V.C. Hills (?) ], 2
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, undated; 14 (Box 1523)
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 1
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 2
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 3
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 4
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 5
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 6
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 7
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 8
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 9
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 10
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 11
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 12
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 13
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 14
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 15
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 16
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 17
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 18
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 19
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 20
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 21
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 22
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 23
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 24
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 25
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 26
    - Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, 27
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado [includes 1 color photograph], undated; 15 (Box 1523)
    - Caption: Great mines on Battle Mountain; Cripple Creek Mining District; Independence in foreground. Two shafts of Portland to the right and the Ajax in the left corner, 1
    - Caption: Vindicator mine; Cripple Creek Mining District, 2
    - Victor High School, now used as the Elementary School for both Victor and Cripple Creek, 3
    - Note: Victor High School, now used as the Elementary School for both Victor and Cripple Creek, 4
    - This is the corner of 4th street and Victor Ave., just south and east of the Gold Coin Mine, where mass meeting was held. Verso: Where my father had his office- and windows from which I watched the riot, 5
    - Verso: Where my father had his office- and windows from which I watched the riot, 5-verso
    - Note: This is the corner of 4th street and Victor Ave., just south and east of the Gold Coin Mine, where mass meeting was held., 6
    - Former home of Dr. Thomas and his family on South 7th Street in Victor, Colorado, 7
    - Note: Former home of Dr. Thomas and his family on South 7th Street in Victor, Colorado, 8
    - Main street in Victor, Colo. at the turn of the century when The Cripple Creek District population was 3 times that of Colo. Springs and almost equal to Denver. 3 railway lines and 2 trolley lines. Caption: Victor Ave., Victor, Colo., 9
    - Note: Main street in Victor, Colo. at the turn of the century when The Cripple Creek District population was 3 times that of Colo. Springs and almost equal to Denver. 3 railway lines and 2 trolley lines, 10
    - Victor-Colorado - as it looked about 1910-15. P.T. City of Gold Mines, 11
    - Verso: Victor-Colorado - as it looked about 1910-15. P.T. City of Gold Mines, 11-verso
    - Note: Gold mines on Battle Mountain above Victor where L.T. worked both as a miner and as a collector of gold samples from lesser mines to bring back to the great Portland Mine assay office, 12
    - Cripple Creek - vistor in mines (Laval Thomas), 13
    - Verso: Cripple Creek - vistor in mines (Laval Thomas), 13-verso
    - [street view, Cripple Creek (?)], 14
    - [Steam Engine], 15
    - [View of town, Cripple Creek (?)], 16
    - [View of town, Cripple Creek (?)], 17
    - [View of Building, Victor, Colorado (?)], 18
    - [Street view of town, Victor Colorado?], 19
    - [Street view of town, Victor Colorado?], 20
    - [Street view of town, Victor Colorado?], 21
    - [View of town, Victor Colorado (?)], 22
    - [View of town, Victor Colorado (?)], 23
    - [View of mines (?), Victor Colorado (?)], 24
    - [View of town, Victor Colorado (?)], 25
    - [View of town, Victor Colorado (?)], 26
    - [group of men], 27
  Box 1524
- Lowell Thomas, 2.1.3.3.3
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado [color photographs], undated; 1 (Box 1524)
    - Ollie Niess, Cripple Creek, 1972, 1
    - Verso: Ollie Niess, Cripple Creek, 1972, 1-verso
    - [view of town, Cripple Creek (?)], 2
    - [view of town, Cripple Creek (?)], 3
    - [view of town, Cripple Creek (?)], 4
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado, undated; 2 (Box 1524)
    - Cresson Mine where recent rich gold strike was made in Cripple Creek District, Colorado [circa 1916] Lowell J. Thomas, 1
    - Verso: Cresson Mine where recent rich gold strike was made in Cripple Creek District, Colorado [circa 1916] Lowell J. Thomas, 1-verso
    - [View of waterfall, two unidentified people], 2
    - [Two women feeding chickens], 3
    - [Waterfall], 4
    - [Farm (?)], 5
    - Katheryn Ryan 3736 grand Doug 4500; 2988 Evan. Geo. Layear- Doras., 6
    - Verso: Katheryn Ryan 3736 grand Doug 4500; 2988 Evan. Geo. Layear- Doras., 6-verso
    - [Man and woman with horse], 7
    - [Man and woman in front of waterfall], 8
    - [View of church (?)], 9
    - [View of house], 10
    - [Group of people at a camp (?)], 11
    - [Group of people in a horse and carriage], 12
    - [View of hills], 13
    - [Group of people on a large rock], 14
    - [View of building, " The Portland G.M.C."], 15
    - [View of town], 16
    - [View of town with train cars in front], 17
    - [Clouds], 18
    - [View of mountains], 19
    - [View of rock formations], 20
    - [Man at a campsite carrying water], 21
    - [Group fo men at a campsite], 22
    - [Campsite with view of the mountains], 23
    - [View of town (?)], 24
  - Lowell Thomas: Cripple Creek Gold Rush, circa 1960s - 1970s; 3 (Box 1524)
    - [Lowell Thomas with printing press (?)], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas holding newspaper with another man], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas in print shop (?)], 3
  - Lowell Thomas: Dog monument, circa 1960s; 4 (Box 1524)
    - [Lowell Thomas with young boy at Balto statue], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with young boy at Balto statue], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas with young boy at Balto statue], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas with young boy at Balto statue], 4
  - Lowell Thomas: Dogs [includes some color photographs], circa 1930s - 1970s; 5 (Box 1524)
    - [Lowell Thomas with dog in the snow], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with dog outdoors], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas with dog outdoors], 3
    - [Lowell thomas with dog and young boy], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas with dog sitting on the steps of a house], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas with dog], 6
    - By S[?] Johnson; Oct 1944, 7
    - Verso: By S[?] Johnson; Oct 1944, 7-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas with dog outside], 8
    - From his 1st bcast [broadcast] studio on Quaker Hill [2 copies], 9
    - Note: From his 1st bcast [broadcast] studio on Quaker Hill, 10
    - [Lowell Thomas with dog, husky (?)], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas playing with, husky (?), dog outside], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas with dog on ski lift], 13
    - L. [left] Monty Atwater, R. [right] Ed LaChappelle; avalanche dog - Precipitation Intensity Factor, PIF, 14
    - Verso: L. [left] Monty Atwater, R. [right] Ed LaChappelle; avalanche dog - Precipitation Intensity Factor, PIF, 14-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas with dog in golf cart (?)], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas with dog in golf cart (?)], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas with dog in golf cart (?)], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas with dog, ( great dane) (?), and ski equipment], 18
    - Note: LT at Alta, Utah, his favorite ski area, 19
  - Lowell Thomas: Early friends and college days, circa 1905 - 1915; 6 (Box 1524)
    - [signed photograph: Lowell Thomas, Jack Pascoe, Gertrude, Allan Dray, Chas. [Esky?], Frances, Ruby, Babe, 1910], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas on the far left with a group of people], 2
    - [View of train station], 3
    - [signed photograph: "A good joke"; Lowell, Gertrude, Charles, Ruby, Jack, Frances, Allan, Babe; circa 1910], 4
    - [group of young people], 5
    - [young woman], 6
    - [young man], 7
    - [young woman and a young man sitting togeher], 8
    - At the University of Northern Indiana (Valparaiso) L.T. collected a B.S. and an M.S. in two years. In this photo he is with the daughters of two professors, 9
    - Note: At the University of Northern Indiana (Valparaiso) L.T. collected a B.S. and an M.S. in two years. In this photo he is with the daughters of two professors, 10
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) and young woman], 11
    - [young woman], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) with two young women], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) with a young woman], 14
    - [Two young women on a bridge (?)], 15
    - [two women and a man], 16
    - [Group of people plowing (?)], 17
    - [Group of men outside a mine], 18
    - [A group of people pushing an early airplane], 19
    - [Group of young men standing on train tracks], 20
    - [Group of young men standing on train tracks, Lowell Thomas on far right with fist raised], 21
    - [man and woman in an office], 22
    - [Group of youg men about to start a race, Lowell Thomas (?) with a starting pistol raised], 23
    - [Young man sitting in the snow], 24
    - [Crowd of people walking around], 25
    - [Train [ Steam engine (?) Coming down the tracks], 26
    - [Woman sitting in the snow], 27
    - [Woman standing in fornt of a snowy hill], 28
    - [Lowell Thomas, and young wman standing on a bridge], 29